{
  "id": "MA3181",
  "GameType": "PairingGame",
  "IntroText": {
    "Type": "PlainText",
    "Content": "將電子鐘與正確的時間配對"
  },
  "introvideo": "MA3181.mp4",
  "GameConfig": {},
  "Questions": [
    [
      {
        "Properties": [
          {
            "Tag": "2",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "06:00"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "4",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "02:37"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "3",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "09:15"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "1",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "07:30"
            }
          }
        ],
        "Pairs": [
          {
            "Question": "上午7時30分",
            "Answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "Question": "上午6時",
            "Answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "Question": "上午9時15分",
            "Answer": "3"
          },
          {
            "Question": "上午2時37分",
            "Answer": "4"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Properties": [
          {
            "Tag": "1",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "10:05"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "3",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "03:25"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "2",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "04:00"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "4",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "01:42"
            }
          }
        ],
        "Pairs": [
          {
            "Question": "上午10時5分",
            "Answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "Question": "上午4時",
            "Answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "Question": "上午3時25分",
            "Answer": "3"
          },
          {
            "Question": "上午1時42分",
            "Answer": "4"
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "Properties": [
          {
            "Tag": "4",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "14:37"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "3",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "21:10"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "2",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "18:00"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "1",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "13:30"
            }
          }
        ],
        "Pairs": [
          {
            "Question": "下午1時30分",
            "Answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "Question": "下午6時",
            "Answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "Question": "下午9時10分",
            "Answer": "3"
          },
          {
            "Question": "下午2時37分",
            "Answer": "4"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Properties": [
          {
            "Tag": "1",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "22:03"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "3",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "15:23"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "4",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "13:41"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "2",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "16:00"
            }
          }
        ],
        "Pairs": [
          {
            "Question": "下午10時3分",
            "Answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "Question": "下午4時",
            "Answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "Question": "下午3時23分",
            "Answer": "3"
          },
          {
            "Question": "下午1時41分",
            "Answer": "4"
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "Properties": [
          {
            "Tag": "1",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "20:30"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "4",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "14:57"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "2",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "05:00"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "3",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "11:01"
            }
          }
        ],
        "Pairs": [
          {
            "Question": "下午8時30分",
            "Answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "Question": "上午5時",
            "Answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "Question": "上午11時1分",
            "Answer": "3"
          },
          {
            "Question": "下午2時57分",
            "Answer": "4"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "Properties": [
          {
            "Tag": "1",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "09:03"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "3",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "18:53"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "2",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "19:00"
            }
          },
          {
            "Tag": "4",
            "Name": "ElectronicClock",
            "Data": {
              "time": "04:40"
            }
          }
        ],
        "Pairs": [
          {
            "Question": "上午9時3分",
            "Answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "Question": "下午7時",
            "Answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "Question": "下午6時53分",
            "Answer": "3"
          },
          {
            "Question": "上午4時40分",
            "Answer": "4"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  ]
}
